The quarrel
Peppa and Suzy Sheep are playing Snap.
Snap! I win!
Peppa and Suzy are best friends.
Snap! I win again!
You cheat it!
I did not!
You looked at the card!
I don't want to play with you anymore.
Oh dear!
Peppa and Suzy have had a quarrel.
Mummy Sheep is here to take Suzy home.
Peppa, say byebye to Suzy.
I am not talking to her.
And I am not talking to her.
Oh, I am sure they will make it up.
They are always best friends really.
It is not funny.
We are not best friends anymore.
Daddy pig is making supper.
Peppa, George, supper time.
It. S spaghetti.
What's the matter, Peppa?
Peppa and Suzy have had a little quarrel.
But I do miss Suzy a bit.
Let's give Suzy a call.
Hello, Mrs. Pig.
May Peppa talk with Suzy, please?
Hello, Suzy!
Hello, Peppa!
We can be friends again if you say sorry.
I'm sorry I said you cheated it,
even though you did cheat.
Well, I'm sorry you ever are my best friend.
It doesn't matter.
I can easily find a new best friend.
It's a lovely sunny day.
All the children are at the playground.
Danny Dog is on the roundabout
with his best friend Pedro Pony.
George is on the seesaw
with his best friend Richard Rabbit.
Seesaw! Seesaw!
Suzy Sheep is on the swings,
on herown.
Peppa is playing mini golf,
Here is Emily elephant.
Can I have a go?
Yeah.
Emily, Suzy Sheep is not
my best friend anymore.
So you can be my best friend.
But my best friend is Candy Cat.
WEE!
Zoey, if you want,
you can be my best friend.
But my best friend is Rebecca Rabbit.
Hello, Suzy!
Hello, Peppa.
Oh, good.
I see you two are friends again.
We are not friends.
We will never be friends again.
I think it's about time
you two make it up.
Peppa, say sorry to Suzy.
Only she says sorry first.
I know, I will count to three,
and you can both say sorry
at the same time.
All right!
One, two, three.
Sorry.
Now you can be best friends again.
Hooray!
Suzy, let's play mini golf.
Good idea!
Peppa and Suzy are best friends again.
Me first!
My go!
My ball went into the hole, so I win.
But my ball knocked it in, so I win.
You are just making the rules up, .
You are making the rules up.
I win!
No, I win!
You two are just the same.
That's why Suzy is my best friend
in the whole world.
And Peppa is my best friend
in the whole world ever.