George's Birthday
Today is George's birthday.
lt is very early in the morning.
George! lt's too early!
Dine-Saw!
Go back to bed!
lt sounds like someone's
up bright and early!
Happy Birthday, George!
George woke me up.
You woke everyone up
on your birthday, Peppa.
That was different.
That was my birthday.
And today is George's birthday.
Happy Birthday, George.
Here's your present, George.
Owwwwww?
Dine-Saw!
l knew it would be some sort of
dinosaurthing.
Squeeze it's tummy!
Too scary!
George.
l've made you a birthday card.
Can you guess
what the picture is?
George can not guess.
l was going to
paint you a flower.
Owwww!
George does not like flowers.
But in the end,
l painted you a...
Dine-saw!
That's a lovely picture, Peppa.
Yes. l am very good at painting.
Now, we're going somewhere
very special for
George's birthday treat!
Yippee! Let's go!
Where are we going?
You'll see.
The family are setting off
forGeorge's birthday treat.
Are we going to the circus?
No. But it's somewhere
just as good.
Um. ls it the cinema?
No. Much better.
l just can't guess.
Where can they be going?
We're here!
The family have
arrived at the museum.
Why are we at the museum?
Come on, you'll see.
What can George's
birthday treat be?
George?
What do you like
best in the whole world?
Dine-Saw!
Oh! Dine-Saw!
George's birthday treat
is a visit to the
museum dinosaur room.
Hu. Silly old dinosaurs again!
Dine-Saw
Whaaaaaaaaa!
Don't be frightened, George,
it's not a real dinosaur.
lt's just a robot.
Look,
l stand on this spot and...
And now,
there's anothersurprise!
All of George and
Peppa's friends are here!
Surprise!
Mummy Rabbit has made
a birthday cake for George.
Can anyone guess
what sort cake it is?
A dinosaurcake?
lt is!
What an amazing guess, Peppa!
Happy Birthday, George!
There's one last surprise.
Follow me!
What is the last surprise?
What do you think it is, Peppa.
lt's probably something
to do with dinosaurs.
Oh. What's that?
lt just needs to be
filled with air...
l know! l know!
lt's a bouncy castle!
Peppa loves bouncy castles!
But if it's for George,
why isn't it a something
to do with dinosaurs?
lt is a dinosaur!
A bouncy dinosaur!
Horray!
George loves bouncy dinosaurs!
Everyone loves bouncy dinosaurs.
This is great!
Happy Birthday, George!