The Tooth Fairy!
Peppa and George are having
their favorite food --- spaghetti!
What a lot of noise!
Finished!
Ah, now we'll have a bit of quiet!
What's that?
It's a tooth!
Where did that come from?
Peppa, maybe you
should look in the mirror!
Oh!
It's my tooth! It's fallen out!
Don't worry, Peppa.
It's just a milk tooth -
They're meant to fall out.
Will I grow a new one, Mummy?
Yes, you will, Peppa.
It also means the Tooth Fairy
will be paying you a visit.
Tooth Fairy?
Yes, the Tooth Fairy.
If you put the tooth under
your pillow tonight,
the Tooth Fairy will come.
The Tooth Fairy will take the tooth.
And in its place,
she will leave a shiny coin!
When I grow up,
I want to be a Tooth Fairy!
And what would you like to be
when you grow up, George?
Dine-Saw!
A dinosaur!
Quick, George, it's bedtime!
We don't want to
miss the Tooth Fairy!
Before going to bed,
Peppa and George brush their teeth.
Peppa, what are you doing?
I'm brushing my tooth
so it is nice and clean
for the Tooth Fairy.
Peppa cannot wait to get into bed.
Peppa is putting her tooth
under the pillow
for the Tooth Fairy.
Goodnight, Peppa and George.
Goodnight, Mummy!
Goodnight, Daddy!
Goodnight, my Little piggies!
George, I'm not going to sleep!
Let's both stay awake all night
and see the Tooth Fairy!
This Tooth Fairy is very late!
The Tooth Fairy is taking
a long time to arrive.
Where is that Tooth Fairy?
What is that noise?
Is it the Tooth Fairy?
George, can you hear something?
Oh, George!
Oh, the noise is George.
He was so tired, he has fallen asleep.
George is not very good
at staying awake, but I am.
I am going to stay awake
and see the Tooth Fairy.
I'm not going to sleep...
The Tooth Fairy has arrived.
But Peppa is asleep.
Hello, Peppa.
Would you like this coin
in return for your tooth?
What a nice, clean tooth.
Thank you, Peppa, Goodnight.
Peppa, George, wake up.
It's morning.
What? I wasn't asleep!
Did the Tooth Fairy come?
No!
Let's take a look under your pillow.
Look, Peppa! The Tooth Fairy
has been and she's left you a coin!
Hurray!
You fell asleep, didn't you?
Well, maybe I fell asleep
just for a Little bit...
Next time, I will stay awake,
and I will see
the Tooth Fairy!