Lunch!
Peppa and George have come to
Granny and Grandpa Pig's
house for lunch.
Granny Pig!
Ganggy lg!
Hello, my little ones!
Would you like to pick some vegetables
from the garden for lunch?
Yes, please!
Grandpa Pig!
Baba lg!
Hello, Peppa, George.
This is Grandpa Pig's vegetable garden.
He has grown all these
vegetables himself!
What's this?
Dinesaw!
A dinosaur!
Let's choose some vegetables for lunch.
Peppa, do you like tomatoes?
Yes, Grandpa Pig!
George, do you like tomatoes?
No.
George does not like tomatoes.
Oh, dear.
Do you both like lettuce?
Yes, Grandpa Pig!
No.
George does not like lettuce.
Oh, dear! I must have something
that George likes.
Do you like cucumber?
Yuck!
George does not like cucumbers,
and he does not like lettuce,
and he does not like tomatoes.
Well, George, what vegetable
do you like?
Chocolate cake!
Silly George! Chocolate cake
isn't a vegetable!
Maybe George will like
the vegetables
when they're made into
a lovely salad.
Ooh! Lovely fresh tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber!
First, we have to wash them!
Peppa and George help Granny Pig
wash the vegetables.
Maybe that's enough washing.
Granny Pig has made
the tomatoes, lettuce
and cucumber into a salad.
Grandpa Pig, can you call
everyone to lunch?
Lunch!!!
Granny Pig has made
pizza for lunch.
And here's some salad
made with Grandpa's tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber!
Chuck in, everyone!
George has eaten his pizza.
But George does not like the tomatoes
or the lettuce or the cucumber.
Oh, dear, George.
Don't you like the salad?
No.
George, just try a little bit
of this lovely tomato.
Yuck!
George. This is cucumber.
Grandpa Pig grew it in his garden!
Errrgh!!
Try a piece of lettuce,
George. It's yummy!
Now, now, George.
Look what I'm doing.
Now, it's a dinosaur!
Dinesaw!
George loves dinosaurs!
George is eating the tomatoes,
lettuce and cucumber!
Well done, George!
Would you like
some more, George?
Full.
George, are you too full
to eat any more tomatoes,
lettuce or cucumber?
George is too full to eat any more.
George, are you too full
to eat anything more?
George is too full
to eat anything more.
Oh, well, then you won't want
any of this CHOCOLATE CAKE!
Chocolate cake!
My word!
George seems to have
got his appetite back!