Fancy Dress Party!
Peppa and George are having
a fancy dress party.
All their friends
are invited.
Peppa is dressed as
a fairy princess.
And George is
dressed as a dinosaur.
Grrrr
Dine-saw!
Here are Peppa's friends,
Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep,
Danny Dog,
Rebecca Rabbit and Pedro Pony.
Suzy is wearing her
nurse's costume.
Hello, Suzy!
Hello, Mr. Pig!
I'm glad the nurse has arrived!
Have you just come from
the hospital?
Er, I'm not a real nurse.
It's just pretend.
Very good. My, my!
Who have we here?
Woof! Woof! I'm a pirate!
Shiver me timbers!
Meow! I'm a witch! I can
turn you into a frog.
Neigh! I'm a clown!
That's funny!
And what are you,
Rebecca Rabbit?
I'm a carrot.
Fantastic! Come in.
There's a fairy princess and a
dinosaur waiting to meet you.
Hello, everyone!
Hello, Peppa!
Baa! Meow! Woof! Neigh!
Hello, Suzy,
I'm Princess Peppa.
You must bow
when you speak to me.
Hello, your majesty.
Baaa!
I'm Nurse Suzy!
Open wide and say "ahhh".
"Ahhh"!
Neigh... I'm a clown.
Do something funny!
Woof! Rebecca, why are you
dressed as a carrot?
I like carrots.
Grrrrrrr!
Dine saw!
A scary dinosaur!
Peppa is admiring herself
in the mirror.
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who is the fairest
of them all?
You are, Peppa.
Meow!
Hello, Peppa.
Hello, I'm a
little fairy princess.
I'm a witch. Meow!
And I've got a magic wand!
I've got a magic wand, too!
I can turn you into a frog.
And I'll turn you into a frog.
Dine saw
Grrrrrrrrr!
Waaaaaaaaaaaa!!!
Oh, dear, George is scared
of his own reflection.
Silly George, look, it's
you in the mirror.
Grrrrr!
Children,
it's time to decide who has
the best fancy dress costume.
We need a judge.
Me! Me!
Me!
As it's Peppa's party,
maybe she should be the judge.
I'm the judge!
Daddy,
what is a "judge"?
The "judge" decides who
has the best costume.
Oh, goody!
Peppa is going to choose
who has the best costume.
Suzy, can I see your
costume, please?
Baaa! I'm Nurse Suzy.
I make people better.
Very good, Nurse Suzy.
Now, Danny!
Woof! I'm a pirate!
Shiver me timbers!
Now, Candy.
Meow. I'm a witch.
I can turn you into a frog!
Well, I'm a fairy princess
and I can turn you into a frog!
Children!
Sorry, Mummy.
Who's next?
I'm a clown!
That's funny!
And Rebecca?
I'm a carrot.
Lovely.
And my little brother, George,
is a scary dinosaur.
Grrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
Everyone's costume is very good.
Hurray!
Baa! Meow! Woof! Neigh!
Now you say who the winner is.
Oh, yes! Uh hum!
And the winner is...
Me!
Peppa you can't pick yourself!
You're the judge!
Oh! Can't I?
You have to pick another winner.
Okay, the carrot wins.
Hurray!
Thank you.
Peppa loves fancy dress parties!
Everyone loves fancy dress parties!