Treasure Hunt!
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig are
making a treasure hunt for
Peppa and Geroge.
Granny Pig is drawing the treasure map.
Grandpa Pig is burying the treasure
in a secret place in the garden.
Grandpa Pig! Have you finished?!
Peppa and George will be here soon!
No need to panic, Granny Pig!
Peppa and her family are here!
Quick, Grandpa Pig! They're here!
Almost done!
Grandpa Pig just finished in time!
Granny Pig! We're here!
Ganggy lg!
Hello, my Little ones!
Grandpa Pig!
Baba lg!
Ahoy there, me hearties!
Peppa, George, we've
made you a treasure hunt!
Somewhere in the garden
is buried treasure!
Wow! Treasure! Where is it?
You have to look for it.
Here's a treasure map for Peppa.
And George can wear my pirate hat.
Ahoy there, Captain George!
The map is a bit difficult.
Daddy, can you help?
Of course, Peppa.
I'm very good with maps.
Er. It is a bit difficult.
Daddy Pig,
you're holding the map upside down!
Yes, I thought as much.
It's easy! The red cross shows
where the treasure is!
But where in the garden are
those two apple trees?
Hmmm... I don't know.
Would you like a clue?
Yes, please!
The first clue is in a bottle.
But where is the bottle?
I can see it!
Peppa has found the first clue.
A message in a bottle.
Look, everyone!
Here's the bottle!
Well done, Peppa!
Let's see what the message says.
Oh it's a message from a pirate!
Mummy? Can you read
the pirate's message?
Hmm... This pirate has
very bad handwriting.
The pirate's handwriting is excellent.
No, I can't make it out at all.
The pirate has clearly written,
"Follow the arrows!"
Follow the arrows?
George has found the second clue!
Sticks in the shape of an arrow!
Look! They point this way!
Peppa and George are
following the arrows.
Look, George! A key!
Peppa has found the next clue. A key!
Well done, Peppa!
Now you just have to find
the treasure chest that it unlocks.
But there aren't any more clues.
Maybe you should take
another look at the map...
Look, Peppa, the map
has two apple trees on it.
Here's an apple tree!
And here's an apple tree!
So the treasure must be here!
Let's take a look!
Oh, dear. There doesn't
seem to be anything here...
Hang on! There is something here!
Wow! Treasure!
Hurray!
Well done! Well done!
I've got the key to open it!
Wow! I can't believe it!
Gold coins! They must be worth a fortune!
It's better than that!
They are not gold coins,
they are chocolate coins!
And there's a chocolate
coin for everybody.
Hurray!
Peppa and George love chocolate coins.
Everyone loves chocolate coins.
Granny, Grandpa,
this is the best treasure hunt ever!