I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother, George.
This is Mummy Pig.
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother, George.
This is Mummy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
Peppa pig.
Mr. Dinosaur is Lost.
George's favourite toy
is Mr. Dinosaur.
DineDine SawSaw.
George loves Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr..
Sometimes, George likes
to scare Peppa with
Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Eeek. Too scary.
At suppertime,
Mr. Dinosaur sits next to George.
I beg your pardon.
Was that you George,
or was it Mr. Dinosaur?
DineDine SawSaw.
At bath time,
George shares his bath
with Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Goodnight, Peppa.
Goodnight, Mummy.
Goodnight, George.
And goodnight, Mr. Dinosaur.
Grrrrrrrrr.
When George goes to bed,
Mr. Dinosaur is tucked up with him.
George's favourite game is
throwing Mr. Dinosaur
up in the air...
Wheeeeeee.
...and catching him
when he falls back down.
Wheeeeeeeee.
Peppa and Daddy Pig are
playing draughts.
I win, Daddy.
Oh, welldone, Peppa.
Whhhhaaaaaaaaaaa.
George?
Whaaaaaaaaa.
George, what's the matter?
Dinosaur...
George, have you
lost Mr. Dinosaur?
George has lost
Mr. Dinosaur.
Don't worry George.
We'll find Mr. Dinosaur.
It's a job for a detective.
Daddy, what is a detective?
A detective is
a very important person
who is good at finding things.
Me. Me. I'm good at
finding things.
Alright. Peppa is the detective.
George. I am the detective.
I will help you find Mr. Dinosaur.
Maybe the detective should ask
George some simple questions.
George? Where's Mr. Dinosaur?
Whaaaaaaaaaa.
George did not know
where Mr. Dinosaur is.
The detective could try and guess
where Mr. Dinosaur might be.
I know. I know where he is.
George always has Mr. Dinosaur
with him in the bath.
So Mr. Dinosaur is in the bath.
Mr. Dinosaur is not in the bath.
Oh. I know.
I know where Mr. Dinosaur is.
George always has Mr.
Dinosaur in his bed at night.
So that's where he is.
Mr. Dinosaur is not in George's bed.
Oh.
Maybe we should try the garden.
Yes, the garden.
I was going to see that.
Where is Mr. Dinosaur?
Mr. Dinosaur is
very hard to find.
Oh. Mr. Dinosaur
isn't anywhere.
George? You do love to throw
Mr. Dinosaur in the air...
I wonder if this time
you threw Mr. Dinosaur
just a bit too high.
There he is. There he is.
I saw him first.
Well done, Peppa.
You really are a
very good detective.
DineDine SawSaw.
Grrrrrrrrrr.
George is so happy to have
Mr. Dinosaur back again.
Wheeeeeeeeee.
Maybe it isn't a good idea
to play with dinosaurs near trees.
Dinosaur.