The New Car!
Today, Peppa and her family
are going for a drive
in their red car.
Shall we have the roof down?
Yes, please!
Peppa and George love their car.
Is everybody ready?
Ready!
Then let's go!
I love our car!
And our car loves us, too!
Don't you?
Oh, dear, the car does not
sound very well.
Hmm!
What's wrong, Daddy?
Hmmm! Er... I don't know.
Let's take it to
Granddad Dog's Garage.
He can fix it.
That's a good idea, Mummy Pig.
Woof!
Granddad Dog runs the garage;
he is very good at mending cars.
Woof! Oh, dear, Daddy Pig!
Your car does not sound very well.
Can you fix it, please,
Granddad Dog?
Yes...
...but it will take all day.
Ohhh...
We wanted to go for a drive in our car.
Woof! Don't worry.
You can borrow this new car
while I fix yours.
Hurray!
Thank you, Granddad Dog.
Would you like the roof down?
Yes, please!
I'll just press this red button.
What a clever car!
Wow.
Woof! When you come back,
I will have fixed your car.
Thank you, Grandad Dog.
Goodbye.
Goodbye!
Bye bye!
Goodbye! Woof!
Peppa and her family
like the new blue car.
There are so many buttons
in this new car.
What does the green button do, Daddy?
Let's see.
Magic windows!
Daddy! Make the magic windows go down.
What does the blue button do?
I don't know. Let's see.
Arrgh!
I love this new car. Can we keep it?
No, we can't keep it, Peppa.
We've only borrowed it for today.
Ohh.
Oh, no, I think it's going to rain.
Yes, I'll just put the roof up.
Now, which is the button
to close the roof?
Oops! Silly me. Aha!
This must be the button.
Arrgh!
The new car has squirted
Daddy Pig with water.
Silly Daddy, that's not the roof!
This button! Oops!
Not that one! This button!
Arrgh! Help!
Daddy Pig has forgotten
which button closes the roof.
I don't think this car likes me!
Let's try the red button.
Hurray!
But now it's stopped raining.
Can we open the roof again?
Er, yes. Which button was it?
The red one! Hurray!
Granddad Dog has fixed the car.
Your car is fixed.
Hurray!
Thank you, Granddad Dog,
and keep the change.
Thank you, Daddy Pig.
Woof! Woof! Goodbye!
Goodbye!
Bye bye!
Ahhh! It's good to get
our old car back again!
I liked the new car
but I like our old car better.
And I think our old car
likes us, too. Don't you?