Ballet Lesson!
Peppa is going to her
first ballet lesson.
This is Madame Gazelle,
the ballet teacher.
Ah, ho! You must be young Peppa!
I am Madame Gazelle!
Hello, Madame!
So sweet!
Welcome to your
first lesson of the ballet!
I'll pick you up later!
Bye bye!
Enjoy yourself!
Here are Peppa's friends,
Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep, Danny Dog,
Rebecca Rabbit, and Pedro Pony.
Children, today we have
a new pupil, Peppa Pig!
Now Peppa, run and join your friends!
Hello, everyone!
Hello, Peppa!
Children! We begin
with demi-plier!
Demi-Plier. Now a
Little jump, petit jete.
With grace and beauty.
Petit jete!
Grace and beauty!
The ballet lesson
is a lot of fun!
Raise you arms!
Lmagine that you are
beautiful swans!
And what noise do you
think a swan might make?
Ah, ho.
Grace and beauty!
Peppa loves dancing!
Everyone loves dancing!
Mummy! Mummy!
We all danced as swans!
Peppa did very well!
I had to dance beautifully
and gracefully!
That's lovely!
Can I show you how I did it?
Let's get home first.
Then you can show Daddy Pig,
and George, and me.
Bye bye!
Peppa and Mummy Pig
are home!
Daddy! George!
I'm going to show you
how to do ballet!
Is it difficult?
It was easy for me.
But you, George, and Mummy
will find it very hard.
First, we need music.
Good. Now, George, Daddy and Mummy,
you must copy what I do.
Madame Gazelle used funny words.
But really, it's just bending
your knees and jumping.
Ah, the petit jete!
Daddy! You know the funny words!
Mummy Pig and I used
to be quite good at ballet!
Do be careful, Daddy Pig.
Our favorite was
the pas de deux!
Hoop-la!
Ooofff! That wasn't quite
how I remembered it.
Silly Daddy Pig!
Maybe we should
leave the ballet to Peppa!
Yes, I am the best at it!
I am a beautiful swan!