My Cousin Chloe!
Peppa and George are
playing in the garden.
To me, George!
You threw the ball too hard, George!
So the rules say,
I win!
Now it's my turn.
I win again!
Peppa, George. Today your big cousin,
Chloe is coming to visit!
Yippee! Cousin Chloe!
George, Chloe is a big girl,
like me.
So, don't be sad if she finds
you too Little to play with.
I'm sure Chloe
will play with both of you.
Chloe is here!
Aunty Pig has brought Chloe to
spend the day at Peppa's house.
Chloe is Peppa and George's cousin.
Chloe is a bit older than
Peppa and George.
Hello, Chloe!
Hello, Peppa! Hello, George!
See you later!
Do you want to play a game?
Yes! Let's play
"Catch!"
Peppa loves playing "Catch".
Do you still play "Catch"?
That's a game for Little children.
We only play "Catch"
because George likes it.
Okay. Let's play it for George.
Do you play with the proper rules
or the baby rules?
Proper rules!
I'll start.
Peppa! You're "it".
Catch me if you can!
Peppa is "it". She has to
chase Chloe and George.
Can't catch me!
George!
I'm going to easily
catch you! You're so Little!
That's not fair!!
You're helping George!
That's because he's Little.
Do you want me to help you?
No! I don't need help.
I'm a big girl like you.
Come on, then, Peppa!
Try and catch us!
Can't catch us!
This is a silly game.
Can we play something else?
Okay, I know a really good
game for big children.
It's called "Sly Fox"!
"Sly Fox"!!
I want to play "Sly Fox"!!
What is it?
One person is the "Sly Fox"
and the others creep
up on them.
Me! Me! I want to
be the "Sly Fox"!
Peppa is the "Sly Fox".
While her back is turned,
the others creep up on her.
But if Peppa turns and
sees someone move,
they have to go back to the start!
George, I saw you move!
Back to the start!
Got you! I win!
You moved before
I was ready!
The rules say I can
move when I like.
Don't they, George?
Now it's Chloe's turn
to be the "Sly Fox".
Peppa and George must
stay very still.
Whoaao!
Peppa! I saw you move!
Back to the start!
It's not fair!
You looked too long!
The rules say, I can look
as long as I want.
Back to the start.
George is the winner!
Can we play a different game?
Yes.
But as long as it's
a grown-up game.
I know!
Let's play my favorite game!
It's very grown-up!
George, do you know
what Peppa's
favorite game is?
Peppa's favorite game is
jumping up and down in muddy puddles!
George, if you jump in puddles,
you must wear your boots!
I've brought some boots
for you too, Chloe!
I'm too grown-up to jump
in muddy puddles.
Oh. So am I.
George loves jumping
in muddy puddles.
Secretly, Peppa would love
to jump in the puddle.
But she wants to look grown-up.
I hear there's some puddle
jumping going on!
Mummy Pig and Daddy Pig love
jumping in muddy puddles!
It does look fun.
Yes, it does.
Maybe there's a rule that says,
big girls can jump in
muddy puddles.
Yes! That's a good rule!
Race you!
Peppa and Chloe love jumping up
and down in muddy puddles!
Everyone loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles,
even grown-up girls!